All of our code basically is going to be inside of this async function main,
我们所有的代码基本上都在这个异步函数 main 中
which is going to be our main script for deploying our simple storage dot soul
它将成为我们用于部署 "SimpleStorage.sol" 的主要脚本
store deploy script is going to replicate exactly what goes on in remix,
storage 部署脚本将精准再现 Remix 中发生的事
in remix, what was the first thing that we always did?
在 Remix 中，我们总要做的第一件事是什么？
Well, the first thing that we would do is actually compile all of our code.
其实就是编译我们所有的代码，对吧？
So we're going to want to compile our code in our JavaScript project as well.
所以我们同样要在这个 JavaScript 项目中先编译我们的代码
In order for us to compile our simple storage contract,
为了编译我们的 SimpleStorage 合约
we're going to use a tool called Silk Jas,
我们将使用一个名为 "solcjs" 的工具
and JavaScript actually has a way
并且 JavaScript 有一个现成的方法
to install projects directly into our setups and into our folders.
可以直接安装项目到我们的配置和文件夹中
If we scroll down this silk Jas is exactly what we're looking for.
如果我们往下拉，这个 solcjs 正是我们要找的东西
Because it has a way to compile a contract that imports other contracts via relative paths,
因为它有种方法能编译通过相对路径导入其它合约的合约
you can see a section in this readme
你可以在 "README"(自述文件) 中看到有这么一部分
and most documentation will have something like this,
并且大多数文档都会有这样的内容
if it's JavaScript compatible. For Node js usage,
只要它与 JavaScript 兼容并且是供 Node.js 使用的
it says to use the latest stable version of the solidity compiler via Node js,
它说的是，为了通过 Node.js 使用最新稳定版本的 Solidity 编译器
you can install it via NPM npm install. So
你可以通过 npm 来安装它 "npm install solc"
NPM is what's known as a package manager.
npm 就是所谓的包管理器("package manager")
And we actually installed NPM just by installing no Jess, right,
其实我们已经在安装 Node.js 的时候安装过 npm 了，是吧？
if we do no dash dash version,
如果我们可以输出 "node --version"
you should also be able to do NPM dash dash version.
那么就应该也可以输出 "npm --version"
Another tool that it comes with is something called core pack.
另一个要用到的工具名字是 "Corepack"
And you can type core pack dash dash version,
你可以输入 "corepack --version" 来确认
now we can install with NPM using npm install silk,
现在我们就可以通过 npm 来执行 "npm install solc" 了
however, I like the yarn package manager a little bit better.
但我其实更喜欢用 "yarn" 包管理器
So we're actually going to install the yarn package manager instead to do all of our package management.
所以我们还需要安装 yarn 包管理器作为我们总的包管理器
If you go to the installation page,
如果你去到安装页面就可以看到
the newer way to install yarn is just by running core pack enable. And the older way is to install with NPM.
较新版本的安装只用运行 "corepack enable"，而旧版本还要使用 npm
If you go ahead and run core pack enable after that finishes,
运行 "corepack enable" 并等待其完成后
you should be able to run yarn dash dash version.
你应该就可以运行 "yarn --version" 了
Alternatively, you can just run NPM i dash g core pack, and then you can run core pack enable.
或者，你需要先运行 "npm i -g corepack" 然后再运行 "corepack enable"
The last option you have is you can run NPM i dash g yarn.
最后一种方法是运行 "npm i -g yarn"
This will install yarn globally for your system.
这会为你的系统全局安装 yarn
But this is considered the outdated way to install yarn.
但这是一种过时的安装 yarn 的方式
And ideally you run core pack enable.
理想情况下你应该运行 "corepack enable"
But in any case, after you run those,
但无论如何，在你运行完那些之后
if you run yarn dash dash version, you should get something that looks like this.
如果你运行 "yarn --version"，都应该得到类似这样的东西
Now that we have yarn, we can actually use yarn to install all of our projects, instead of NPM.
现在我们有了 yarn 就能用它来安装所有的项目了，而不是用 npm
Back in silk Jas where it says npm install soak,
回到 solcjs，它说的是 "npm install solc"
we can do the yarn equivalents of NPM install sock,
我们可以用 yarn 达到完全相同的效果
which is going to be yarn, add sock,
具体做法就是 "yarn add solc"
this will actually go ahead and install solc to our project.
这就能为我们的项目安装 solc 了
If we open up our folders, you'll actually see that this added a couple of different folders,
打开我们的文件夹，可以看到这里已经添加了一些不同的文件夹
it first added a package dot JSON
首先是这个 "package.json" 文件
package dot JSON is a file that tells us a lot about our project and the dependencies that it works with.
"package.json" 是一个描述我们的项目以及它的依赖关系的文件
For example, we've installed the soap package of 0.8 point 13.
举个例子，我们安装了 "solc" 包 0.8.13 版本
Our yarn dot lock tells us the exact version of all the different packages of our project.
而 "yarn.lock" 可以告诉我们项目所使用的所有不同的包的确切版本
For example, the reason this is so important too,
举个例子，这个东西之所以重要
is solc has a ton of dependencies as well.
是因为 solc 自己也有大量的依赖项
So yarn dot lock tells us exactly what version of solc
所以 "yarn.lock" 能告诉我们 solc 的确切版本
and all the different dependencies of solchen. Any other project that we add.
以及我们添加的所有 solc 所依赖的项目的版本
This is autogenerated file, don't edit the file directly.
这一个自动生成的文件，不要直接编辑本文件
The final bit is we got this node modules folder.
最后一点是我们得到了这个 "node_modules" 文件夹
This node modules folder is going to be where all the installed code that we just downloaded is,
这个文件夹就存放着我们刚刚下载的所有代码
for example, if we look at node modules, we can see there's a sock folder.
比如如果我们查看 "node_modules"，能看到一个 solc 文件夹
And inside this sock folder
而在这个 solc 文件夹里的
is all the code associated with this soap package that we just installed.
就是我们刚刚下载的这个 solc 包的所有相关代码
And since we're working with zero point 8.7 of slowly,
因为我们正在使用的是 0.8.7 版本的 Solidity
we actually want to install that specific version.
所以我们实际要安装这个的特定版本
So we're going to do yarn add solc at zero point 8.7 Dash fixed
我们要做的就是 "yarn add solc@0.8.7-fixed"
and you'll see in our package dot JSON
现在你可以在 "package.json" 里看到
you can now see zero point 8.7 Dash fixed in our dependencies section for sulk.
solc 的依赖项("dependencies")部分变成了 "0.8.0-fixed"
Normally you can just add your salt version like yarn add zero point 8.7
一般来说你添加的会是 "yarn add 0.8.7" 这样的版本号
But there was an issue with zero point 8.7
但 0.8.7 版本存在一些问题
So we had to do zero point 8.7 Dash fixed.
所以我们不得不使用 "0.8.7-fixed" 版本
You can find the different releases and the different versions
你可以找到不同发行版("Releases")和不同版本
if you go to sulk Jas releases and then to tags
就在 solcjs 的 "Releases" 里接着选择 "Tags"
Alright, great. Now that we have sold, we have the ability to
actually compile our contracts, we could either compile them in
our code and have it automatically run whenever we
hit Deploy, or, or we could compile them separately. If you
want to go back after this section is an example in the
sculpt Jas repository that shows you how to actually compile silk
right in your code. We are actually going to compile them
separately using a soap Jas command. The yarn command is
both used to install dependencies and it can be used
to run scripts. If you go to sulk Jas and you scroll down, it
says in order to use the command line, you actually need to
install it globally. If you want to install this globally using
yarn Global Add solc at zero point 8.7 Dash fixed you can
absolutely go ahead. However, since we're inside of this
folder here, which has the yarn dot lock the package json and
the node modules yarn will be smart enough to know i You're
looking for the soak in this folder. So we can actually go
ahead and compile our contract using yarn and solc Jess if you
want to see all the different commands soak Jas allows we can
just run yarn. So Jas dash dash help, and you'll see it'll spit
out a list of all the different options that soft Jas has. You
can also run yarn, so Jas dash dash version to just make sure
that we're on the correct version, which is indeed zero
point 8.7. Now to actually compile our simple storage at
soul, let's run the compliation command we will run yarn, so J
S, dash dash bin since we want the binary dash dash ABI since
we also want the ABI dash dash include path node modules. Since
we want to include any contracts or files in our node modules, we
aren't using any for this project, but in the future, you
will need to include this dash dash include path node modules
do dash dash base path of period, this period means that
the base path is going to be this folder dash O period, which
means we're going to output the compiled binary and ABI to this
folder. And then finally, simple storage dot soul. Since this is
the contract that we want to compile, auto completed it from
simple storage to simple storage. So by typing simple,
and then hitting Tab, but let's go ahead and hit enter, you'll
see it's running this command to compile this contract. And
you'll see two files get output. One called Simple Storage soul
underscore simple storage that API in simple storage Sol
underscore simple storage dot bin, the ABI is obviously the
ABI of this contract, which will need in the future. And then the
bin is going to be the binary, or the really low level of this
code back and remix. If you compile simple storage, that
soul, you can actually look at compliation details, like the
ABI which we just got, or the bytecode, which if you look at
this object 60806 That's the same as the binary here 60806.
Alright, great. So now we've compiled our contracts here.
Now, obviously, now if you hit up on your keyboard, you can
actually cycle through your most recent terminal commands. And if
you hit up enough, we can see this command that we just ran
typing this out or hitting up a whole bunch every single time,
it's going to be really annoying to do anytime we want to
recompile. So what we can do is we can add a script section in
our package dot JSON to shorten some yarn scripts for us. So
what we'll do is back in our package, dot JSON, a lot of
comma, and we'll add a section called scripts, add the colon
and the brackets. And in here, we'll say anytime we say
compile, we will run this long command. So I'd compile we'll
put some quotes. And we'll paste that in there. So now instead of
typing that whole thing out, as long as we're in the same folder
that our package json is in, we can run yarn compile. And this
will run that whole script for us without us having to type the
whole thing out scripts are a really useful way to make it
easier for us to run long commands. All right, great. Now
we have our code compiled, this is going to be equivalent to US
hitting this compile button for us to actually go ahead and
deploy.